RAHEEB HASSAN

a raheeb.xyz

raheeb998@gmail.com

٤.

, +880 1521 517218

github.com/hoenchioma

0

Dhaka, Bangladesh

in /in/raheebhassan

SUMMARY

An inquisitive, passionate, and tenacious individual with an aptitude for problem-solving. Recently graduated with the 2nd highest CGPA in my class from the University of Dhaka and currently working as an Associate Machine Learning Engineer at Therap Services LLC. Research interests encompass decentralized learning, reinforcement learning, multi-agent systems, game theory, and optimization. Have authored papers under review in Applied Intelligence (Journal) and ICAPS 2024. Also enjoy doing competitive programming and cybersecurity competitions.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2023 University of Dhaka

BSc. (Hons)

Department of Computer Science and Engineering CGPA: 3.75 (2nd highest in my class)

EXPERIENCE

2/2023 -

Associate Machine Learning Engineer

Therap Services LLC

- · Worked with computer vision, face recognition, multi-object tracking, activity recognition
- · Worked with the NVIDIA Deepstream platform for low level machine learning computation
- · Designed and implemented systems for ML based real time monitoring

2021 - 2023

Undergraduate Research Student

Cognitive Agents and Learning Lab (CAIL), University of Dhaka

· Worked on Mutli-Agent Reinforcement Learning and Safe RL

2020 - 2021 (Part-Time)

Full Stack Developer

CranTech LLC (Formerly Quixx Projects)

- Worked on several frontend projects like Shoshikkha, Amplfiy, etc.
- Worked with ReactJS (frontend), ExpressJS (backend) and React Native (Mobile)

RESEARCH

In Review

DePAint: A Decentralized Safe Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Algorithm considering Peak and Average Constraints Applied Intelligence Journal

Authors: Raheeb Hassan, K.M. Shadman Wadith, Md. Mamun or Rashid, Md. Mosaddek Khan

Keywords: Decentralized Learning, Reinforcement Learning (RL), Mutli Agent RL, Safe RL, Peak Constraint, Average Constraint

Preprint: https://arxiv.org/abs/2310.14348

In Review

A Graph Neural Network-Based QUBO-Formulated Hamiltonian-Inspired Loss Function for Combinatorial Optimization using Reinforcement Learning ICAPS 2024

Author: Redwan Ahmed Rizvee, Raheeb Hassan, Md. Mosaddek Khan

Keywords: Hamiltonian Function, Deep Reinforcement Learning, Graph Neural Network, Monte Carlo Tree Search

Preprint: https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.16277

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

Awards Best Poster Presentation Award

Undergraduate Project Final Poster Presentation 2021 (Held on Jan 2023) Department of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Dhaka

Topic: DePAint: A Decentralized Safe Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Algorithm considering Peak and Average Constraints

Competitions

- · Code Samurai: Inter-University Hackathon 2022 (Champion)
- SUST Technovent 2023 Capture the Flag (**11th place**)
- International Collegiate Programming Contest Asia Dhaka Regional 2021 (16th place)
- MIST Inter University Programming Contest 2019 (20th place)
- SUB Inter University Programming Contest 2019 (28th place)

Online Judge

· Solved 90+ problems on LightOJ

· Expert (rating 1647) on Codeforces

· Blue (rating 1744) on Codechef

PROJECTS

https://github.com/hoenchioma/kamlabot kamlabot Python

Al-powered helper chatbot for fetching various useful info (like class routine, syllabus, etc.)

Uses NLP to parse message intent and fetch data from Firebase Database

Unity, C#, **Trojan Capture The Flag**

Python A capture-the-flag game with AI-powered agents who can deceive you

Trained agents using multi agent reinforcement learning (MA-POCA)

github.com/hoenchioma/hotkey Android, Java,

C/C++ A cross-platform solution for controlling your PC from a mobile device

Python vlawyer github.com/hoenchioma/vlawyer

An unofficial vjudge statistics API

SFML, OpenGL, **Depths of CSEDU** github.com/hoenchioma/Depths-of-CSEDU

C/C++ Top-down horror/adventure RPG

Corona Factcheck github.com/Viper4717/corona-factcheck-frontend ReactJS, NodeJS,

Strapi A website for fact-checking Corona-related information

STANDARDIZED TESTS

GRE Quantitative Reasoning: **TOEFL** Total: 113 161

Verbal Reasoning: 162 Reading: 30 Analytical Writing: 4.0 Listening: 29 Speaking: 27

Writing: 27

SKILLS

Python, C++, C, Java, Javascript, Typescript, C# (Unity3D), Dart (Flutter) Languages:

Data Science: Pandas, Numpy, Sympy, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Scrapy, Beautiful Soup, Selenium.

Machine

PyTorch, TorchVision, NVIDIA DeepStream, Scikit-Learn.

Learning: